arcteryx.com 2017-07-06

# Privacy Policy / Arc'teryx

**Head Office Info**

Arc’teryx Equipment   
a Division of Amer Sports Canada Inc.  
110 - 2220 Dollarton Hwy  
North Vancouver, BC  
Canada V7H 1A8

**Main Reception:**  
Phone: 604.960-3001  
Fax: 604.904-3692

Print Privacy Policy

Arc’teryx Equipment a Division of Amer Sports Canada Inc. is a worldwide leader in the performance soft goods industry.

This Privacy Policy applies to Arc’teryx Equipment a Division of Amer Sports Canada Inc and its affiliates ("Arc'teryx", "we", "us", "our") and explains how we collect, use and disclose personal information. This policy describes the type of information we collect and use, how we will protect it, when we may disclose it, and how you can update your information.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to personal information about employees, partners or other staff, consultants, volunteers or other individuals assigned to Arc'teryx (collectively, "Arc'teryx Members"), or to any information which is not personal information as defined in or interpreted under applicable Canadian law.

## Clear User’s consent: 

**By using the relevant website / or by submitting personal data to Arc’teryx / or by clicking “I Agree”, depending on the website, service, or application you are using, you express your consent and agreement to the processing of your personal data in the manner provided in this Policy. If you do not agree with this policy, please do not use the website, or provide Arc’teryx with your personal data, or do not grant your consent otherwise.**

## Privacy in General

At Arc'teryx, we respect your privacy. Arc'teryx will never sell, trade, rent or loan your personal information to any other organization. "Personal information" is information about an identifiable individual as described in applicable privacy legislation.

At Arc'teryx, we take steps to ensure we meet the privacy principles and requirements for personal information under Canadian law. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform our customers, visitors and other individuals we deal with ("you" or "your") about how we collect, use, and disclose personal information in our custody or control.

## Consent

We collect, use and disclose your personal information with your consent or as permitted or required by law. Your consent may be expressed, depending on the circumstances and the sensitivity of the personal information in question. In most cases, your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information by Arc'teryx may be implied by the fact that you have contacted us or purchased our goods or services and voluntarily provided your personal information to us. If you provide personal information about another person to us, we assume you have the consent of that individual to enable us to collect, use or disclose their information and described in this policy.

If you choose to provide your personal information to Arc'teryx we assume that you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy.

You may refuse consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information subject to legal and contractual requirements as well as reasonable notice. If you do not consent, please do not provide us with your personal information. Where applicable, please exercise the opt-in or opt-out options offered to you on our website or in our dealings with you. You may also withdraw your consent to our further collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by contacting our Privacy Officer at [privacy@arcteryx.com](mailto:privacy@arcteryx.com) or at 1-866-458-2473 . Please note that if you withdraw your consent to our use of your personal information, we may no longer be able to provide you with certain of our services.

There are instances where Arc'teryx may collect, use or disclose your personal information without your consent. For example, we may use or disclose your personal information to comply with a subpoena or court order, under applicable law, or to collect a debt you owe to us.

## What Personal Information is Collected and How it is Used

We collect personal information directly from you or through our interactions with you or about you. Arc'teryx may ask you to provide your personal information (including your address, date of birth, telephone number, e-mail address or work affiliation), your credit card or other financial information, or information about your opinions or preferences with respect to participation in events, programs or services offered by Arc'teryx from time to time, We also collect personal information like your product preferences, store preferences, and other information when you complete our surveys, enter our contests, or otherwise complete Arc'teryx forms.

Authorized Arc'teryx Members, our agents and service providers may have access to your personal information. We use or disclose your personal information to, as applicable, provide you with products or services, register purchased products and otherwise manage our relationship with you, improve our website and marketing practices, and to administer our events, programs or other services. We may use your personal information to offer products or services to you, communicate with you regarding the products, services or information at your request, administer our customer databases, process and collect our accounts, send you surveys, catalogues, e-mails, or other notifications of Arc'teryx products, events and offers, invite you to Arc'teryx events, and as otherwise permitted or required by law or for purposes for which you otherwise provide your consent. If you do not wish to receive information from us about our products, services or events, you may ask us not to contact you for these purposes.

We may disclose the personal information we collect from you in certain circumstances, including:

  * where you have expressly or implicitly asked us to disclose your personal information to a third-party for a designated purpose (for example, to obtain credit or to attend an Arc'teryx sponsored event);
  * where we reasonably believe a third-party requesting your personal information is your agent;
  * if we are required or authorized by law to do so (for example, if a court issues a subpoena or order);
  * as necessary to meet legal, contractual, regulatory, insurance, audit and security requirements or as is otherwise permitted or required by law.

## Our Website

We may collect personal information about you when you use our website. For example, we collect the personal information you tell us about yourself when you complete our online forms, when you request information through the "Contact Us" page of our website, or when you send us an e-mail.

We track usage patterns on our website on an anonymous basis as most websites do. Each time you visit our website, our server may record your internet service provider, browser, the date and time of your visit, the pages you visit, the documents downloaded, the searches you performed, and the referring URL you came from. We use this non-personal information to optimize your website experience.

## Use of Cookies 

We may also employ "cookies" (a small text file that a website can use to identify your computer) or similar technology that provides additional functionality to our website and helps us analyze website usage more accurately. Cookies allow for a personalized experience when you visit or revisit our site. Our web server may automatically recognize your registered user's domain name and e-mail address or recognize you as a return visitor to our site. Arc'teryx may collect information on what pages you access or view as well as any information you volunteer such as survey information and/or site registrations. Cookies also record session information such as items that you add to your shopping cart, and can be used to retain those items in your shopping cart on your next visit. We may also use these cookies to present you with relevant products or advertisements within and beyond the Arc’teryx website. You can set your web browser to disable cookies but if you do some features of our website may not function normally.

For your convenience, we offer links from our website to other websites. If you link to another website from our website, please consult the privacy policy of that site before providing any of your personal information. Arc'teryx is not responsible for, nor do we accept any liability for, the privacy practices or content of any websites which we do not directly control.

## Minors 

## Children under the Age of 13

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not send us any information about yourself including your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address. In the event we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under 13 without parental consent, we will delete this information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we may have received information from or about a child under the age of 13 please contact us at [privacy@arcteryx.com](mailto:privacy@arcteryx.com) or 1-866-458-2473 .

## Minors over the age of 13

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask a parent or guardian for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone, including us, over the Internet.

## Our Security Measures for Personal Information

Arc'teryx may transfer your personal information to service providers who administer or provide products, services or information on our behalf. We use reasonable measures to require the organizations with whom we share your personal information use your personal information only to perform the services we have hired them to provide.

Some of the service providers that process or handle personal information on our behalf are located outside of Canada. As a result, your personal information may be transferred, stored and/or processed outside of Canada in connection with the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Contractual or other measures we may use to protect your personal information are subject to the legal requirements of the foreign jurisdictions where your personal information may be transferred, stored or processed. For example, there may be lawful requirements in those jurisdictions to disclose personal information to government authorities in those countries.

## How to Update or Change your Personal Information

Arc'teryx maintains your personal information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. If you would like to request access to or correction of your personal information in Arc'teryx' custody or control, please make your request in writing to our Privacy Officer at Arc'teryx, Suite 110, 2220 Dollarton Highway, North Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada V7H 1A8. We may need to verify your identity before searching for and providing you with your personal information. In some circumstances, we may not provide access to your personal information if, for example, it contains the personal information of other people, if it constitutes confidential commercial information, or if it otherwise is not properly the subject of an access request.

We predominantly use your personal information to provide you with timely products, services, and news of our events. It is important that your personal information be accurate and up-to-date. Please inform us of any changes to your personal information as soon as possible.

## Opting Out

In case you wish to know what personal data we hold about you or you wish to replenish, rectify, anonymize or delere any incomplete, incorrect or outdated personal data, or you wish us to cease processing your personal data for the purposes of sending promotional materials or direct marketing or for the performance of market research or on other compelling legal grounds, you may, as appropriate and in accordance with applicable law, exercise such rights by contacting us through the contact points referred to below. In some cases, especially if you wish us to delete or cease the processing of your personal data, this may also mean that we may not be able to continue to provide the services to you. We encourage you to use available profile management tools for the above purposes as such tools often provide you with direct access to your personal data and allow you to effectively manage it.

Please note that Arc’teryx may need to identify you and to ask for additional information in order to be able to fulfill your above request. Please also note that applicable law may contain restrictions and other provisions that relate to your above rights.

## The Controller of Your Personal Data and Contact Details

Privacy Officer at Arc'teryx, Suite 110, 2220 Dollarton Highway, North Vancouver, British Columbia Canada V7H 1A8, by e-mail at [privacy@arcteryx.com](mailto:privacy@arcteryx.com) or by telephone at 1-866-458-2473. 

In the event of changes or opt-out requests, Arc'teryx may retain the personal information necessary for record-keeping in connection with your past transactions as well as any product registrations or warranties.

## Questions or Comments

If you have questions or comments about our personal information practices, please contact our Privacy Officer at Arc'teryx, Suite 110, 2220 Dollarton Highway, North Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada V7H 1A8, by e-mail at [privacy@arcteryx.com](mailto:privacy@arcteryx.com), or by telephone at 1-866-458-2473.

You may contact us at the address, e-mail address or telephone above to obtain a current copy of our Privacy Policy.

Questions about our website should be directed to our webmaster at [webmaster@arcteryx.com](mailto:webmaster@arcteryx.com "Website Questions") or at 1-866-458-2473.

## Certain Legalities

Arc'teryx reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check back from time to time to ensure you are aware of and accept any changes made to this Privacy Policy. Continued use of our website signifies your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy as updated or amended.

This Privacy Policy and all of its graphics, logos, trademarks, and other intellectual property are the property of Arc'teryx and protected by copyright, trademark and other intellectual property laws. No reproduction of our intellectual property is allowed without Arc'teryx' express written consent.

## Thank You

Thank you for taking the time to review this important information concerning our Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy is effective on April 15, 2014 and may be revised from time to time.

Arc’teryx Equipment a Division of Amer Sports Canada Inc.

* * *

## Política de privacidad de Arc’teryx

Arc’teryx Equipment a Division of Amer Sports Canada Inc. es una marca líder internacional en el sector de bienes blandos.

La presente política de privacidad se aplica a Arc’teryx Equipment a Division of Amer Sports Canada Inc. y a sus afiliados («Arc'teryx», «nosotros», «nos», «nuestro(s)», «nuestra(s)») y explica cómo recogemos, utilizamos y divulgamos la información personal. Esta política describe el tipo de información que recogemos y utilizamos, cómo la protegemos, cuándo podemos divulgarla y cómo podemos actualizarla.

La presente política de privacidad no es aplicable a la información personal de empleados, socios y otros miembros de la plantilla, consultores, voluntarios y otras personas vinculadas a Arc’teryx (conjuntamente, «miembros de Arc’teryx»), o a aquella información que no se considere información personal, según lo dispuesto e interpretado por la legislación canadiense aplicable.

## Consentimiento claro del usuario: 

**Al utilizar el sitio web, enviar datos personales a Arc’teryx o hacer clic en «Aceptar», dependiendo del sitio web, servicio o aplicación que esté utilizando, usted manifiesta su consentimiento al procesamiento de sus datos personales en la forma definida en esta política. Si no está de acuerdo con esta política, le rogamos que no utilice el sitio web, no envíe sus datos personales a Arc’teryx o no otorgue su consentimiento.**

## Privacidad: términos generales

En Arc’teryx respetamos su privacidad. Arc’teryx nunca venderá, comercializará, alquilará o prestará sus datos personales a otras organizaciones. «Información personal» es aquella información sobre una persona física identificable, tal como se define en la legislación sobre privacidad aplicable.

En Arc’teryx, tomamos las medidas necesarias para garantizar que cumplimos los principios y requisitos de privacidad de la información personal según la legislación canadiense. La finalidad de esta política de privacidad es informar a nuestros clientes, visitantes y otras personas con las que tratamos («usted» o «su(s)») sobre la manera en la que recogemos, utilizamos y divulgamos la información personal que se encuentra bajo nuestra custodia o control.

## Consentimiento

Solo recogemos, utilizamos y divulgamos su información personal con su consentimiento o según lo permita o exija la legislación vigente. Puede expresar su consentimiento dependiendo de las circunstancias y de la confidencialidad de la información personal en cuestión. En la mayoría de los casos, su consentimiento a que Arc’teryx recoja, utilice y divulgue su información personal puede estar implícito al ponerse en contacto con nosotros o adquirir nuestros productos o servicios y al facilitarnos voluntariamente su información personal. Si nos facilita información personal sobre otra persona, asumimos que cuenta con el consentimiento de dicha persona, lo que nos permite recoger, utilizar o divulgar su información tal como se describe en esta política.

Si opta por facilitar su información personal a Arc’teryx, asumimos que consiente que recojamos, utilicemos y divulguemos su información personal tal como se estipula en esta política.

Puede negar su consentimiento a que recojamos, utilicemos y divulguemos su información personal a reserva de requisitos legales y contractuales, así como de un aviso razonable. Si no está de acuerdo, le rogamos que no nos facilite su información personal. Cuando proceda, puede seleccionar si desea excluir o incluir voluntariamente algún dato en nuestro sitio web o en nuestro trato con usted. También puede retirar su consentimiento a que sigamos recogiendo, utilizando y divulgando su información personal poniéndose en contacto con nuestro responsable de Privacidad mediante correo electrónico ([privacy@arcteryx.com](mailto:privacy@arcteryx.com)) o llamando al 1-866-458-2473 . Por favor, tenga en cuenta que si retira su consentimiento a que utilicemos su información personal, es posible que ya no podamos ofrecerle algunos de nuestros servicios.

Hay casos en los que Arc’teryx puede recoger, utilizar o divulgar su información personal sin su consentimiento. Por ejemplo, podemos utilizar o divulgar su información personal para cumplir con una citación legal o una orden judicial, según la legislación aplicable, o para recuperar una deuda. 

## Qué información personal se recoge y cómo se utiliza

Recogemos información personal directamente de usted o de nuestras interacciones con usted o sobre usted. Arc’teryx puede solicitar que nos facilite su información personal (incluyendo dirección, fecha de nacimiento, número de teléfono, dirección de correo electrónico o afiliación laboral), su tarjeta de crédito u otra información financiera, o información acerca de sus opiniones o preferencias con respecto a la participación en eventos, programas o servicios ofrecidos por Arc’teryx puntualmente. También recogemos información personal como preferencias de productos o tiendas y otro tipo de información al rellenar encuestas, participar en nuestros concursos o completar cualquier otro formulario de Arc’teryx.

Es posible que miembros autorizados de Arc’teryx, agentes y proveedores tengan acceso a su información personal. Utilizamos o divulgamos su información personal para, según proceda, ofrecerle productos o servicios, registrar los productos que ha adquirido y gestionar nuestra relación con usted, mejorar nuestro sitio web y prácticas de marketing y administrar nuestros eventos, programas y otros servicios. Podemos utilizar su información personal para ofrecerle productos y servicios, comunicarnos con usted con relación a los productos, servicios o información que solicite, administrar nuestras bases de datos de clientes, procesar y recopilar nuestras cuentas, enviarle encuestas, catálogos, mensajes de correo electrónico u otras notificaciones sobre productos Arc’teryx, eventos y ofertas, invitarle a eventos organizados por Arc’teryx, y por cualquier otro motivo permitido o requerido por la ley o para los fines para los que usted dio su consentimiento. Si no desea que le enviemos información sobre nuestros productos, servicios o eventos, puede pedirnos que no nos pongamos en contacto con usted con este fin.

Podemos divulgar la información personal que recogemos en determinadas circunstancias, como:

  * si ha solicitado expresa o implícitamente que divulguemos su información personal a un tercero para un determinado propósito (por ejemplo, para obtener crédito o para asistir a un evento patrocinado por Arc’teryx);
  * si tenemos razones para pensar que una tercera persona que solicita su información personal es agente suyo;
  * si la ley nos lo exige o nos autoriza a ello (por ejemplo, en caso de citación legal u orden judicial);
  * según sea necesario para cumplir requisitos legales, contractuales, normativos, de seguro, de auditoría o de seguridad, o si la legislación lo permite o lo exige.

## Nuestro sitio web

Podemos recoger información personal sobre usted cuando utilice nuestro sitio web. Por ejemplo, recogemos la información personal que nos facilita sobre usted cuando rellena nuestros formularios en internet, cuando solicita información a través de la página «Contacto», o cuando nos envía un mensaje de correo electrónico.

Registramos patrones de uso en nuestro sitio web de forma anónima, como la mayoría de sitios web. Cada vez que visita nuestro sitio web, nuestro servidor puede registrar su proveedor de internet, navegador, la fecha y hora de su visita, las páginas que visita, los documentos descargados, las búsquedas realizadas y la URL de referencia de la que proviene. Utilizamos esta información de carácter no personal para optimizar su experiencia en nuestro sitio web.

## Uso de cookies 

También podemos utilizar «cookies» (un pequeño archivo de texto que puede utilizar un sitio web para identificar su ordenador) o una tecnología similar que proporcione una funcionalidad adicional a nuestro sitio web y nos ayude a analizar el uso del sitio de una manera más precisa. Las cookies nos permiten ofrecerle una experiencia personalizada cuando visite o vuelva a visitar nuestro sitio. Nuestro servidor web puede reconocer automáticamente el nombre del dominio registrado de un usuario y las direcciones de correo electrónico o reconocerle en la próxima visita a nuestro sitio. Arc’teryx puede recoger información sobre las páginas a las que accede o que visita, además de información que nos suministre voluntariamente, como información recogida en encuestas o inscripciones en sitios. Las cookies también registran información sobre la sesión, como qué artículos añade a su cesta de la compra, y pueden utilizarla para retener dichos artículos en su cesta de la compra la próxima visita. También podemos utilizar las cookies para presentarle productos o anuncios relevantes dentro o fuera del sitio web de Arc’teryx. Puede configurar su navegador web para deshabilitar las cookies, pero si lo hace, es posible que algunas de las funciones de nuestro sitio web no funcionen normalmente.

Para su comodidad, ofrecemos enlaces en nuestro sitio web a otros sitios web. Si accede a otro sitio web a partir del nuestro, le recomendamos que consulte la política de privacidad de dicho sitio antes de facilitar algún tipo de información personal. Arc’teryx no es responsable ni asume ninguna responsabilidad por las prácticas de privacidad o el contenido de otros sitios web que no controlamos directamente.

## Menores de edad 

## Niños menores de 13 años

No recogemos o solicitamos, de forma deliberada, información personal de ninguna persona menor de 13 años. Si es menor de 13 años, no nos envíe ninguna información sobre usted, como su nombre, dirección, número de teléfono o dirección de correo electrónico. Si descubrimos que hemos recogido información personal de un niño menor de 13 años sin el consentimiento de sus padres, eliminaremos dicha información lo antes posible. Si cree que podemos haber recibido información que provenga o trate de un niño menor de 13 años, le rogamos que se ponga en contacto con nosotros mediante correo electrónico ([privacy@arcteryx.com](mailto:privacy@arcteryx.com)) o nos llame al 1-866-458-2473 .

## Menores de edad con más de 13 años

Recomendamos que los menores de edad con más de 13 años pidan permiso a sus padres o tutores antes de enviar información personal a terceros, incluidos nosotros, a través de internet.

## Medidas de seguridad con respecto a la información personal

Arc’teryx puede transferir su información personal a proveedores que administren o suministren productos, servicios o información en nuestro nombre. Tomamos medidas razonables para exigir a las organizaciones con las que compartimos su información personal que utilicen dicha información únicamente para prestar los servicios para los que los hemos contratado.

Algunos de los proveedores que procesan o manejan información personal en nuestro nombre están ubicados fuera de Canadá. Como consecuencia, es posible que su información personal se transfiera, almacene y/o procese fuera de Canadá, en relación con los fines descritos en esta política de privacidad. Las medidas contractuales o de otra naturaleza que podemos utilizar para proteger su información personal están sujetas a los requisitos legales de las jurisdicciones extranjeras en las que su información personal sea transferida, almacenada o procesada. Por ejemplo, pueden existir requisitos legales en dichas jurisdicciones que exijan la divulgación de la información personal a las autoridades gubernamentales de dichos países.

## Cómo actualizar o modificar su información personal

Arc’teryx conserva su información personal para los fines establecidos en esta política de privacidad. Si desea corregir o solicitar acceso a información personal sobre usted que se encuentre bajo la custodia o control de Arc’teryx, realice su solicitud por escrito al responsable de Privacidad y envíela a la siguiente dirección: Arc'teryx, Suite 110, 2220 Dollarton Highway, North Vancouver, Columbia Británica, Canadá V7H 1A8. Es posible que necesitemos comprobar su identidad antes de buscar y facilitarle su información personal. En algunos casos, es posible que no podamos facilitarle el acceso a dicha información si, por ejemplo, contiene información personal de terceros, si constituye información comercial confidencial o si no es propiamente objeto de una solicitud de acceso.

Utilizamos su información personal, principalmente, para ofrecerle productos y servicios oportunos, además de noticias de nuestros eventos. Es importante que su información personal sea precisa y esté actualizada. Le rogamos que nos informe de cualquier cambio en su información personal tan pronto como sea posible.

## Exclusión de datos

Si desea saber qué datos personales almacenamos sobre usted o rellenar, rectificar, anonimizar o eliminar cualquier dato personal incompleto, incorrecto u obsoleto, o si desea que dejemos de procesar sus datos personales al objeto de enviarle materiales promocionales o marketing directo, o para la realización de investigaciones de mercado o por otras razones legales, puede, según el caso y conforme a la legislación aplicable, ejercitar tales derechos poniéndose en contacto con nosotros en los puntos de contacto que se detallan más abajo. En algunos casos, especialmente si desea que eliminemos o suspendamos el procesamiento de sus datos personales, es posible que implique que no podamos seguir prestándole algunos servicios. Le animamos a que utilice las herramientas de gestión de perfil disponibles para los fines especificados anteriormente, ya que dichas herramientas le suelen ofrecer acceso directo a sus datos personales y le permiten gestionarlos eficazmente.

Por favor, tenga en cuenta que Arc’teryx puede necesitar identificarle y solicitarle información adicional para poder llevar a cabo las peticiones anteriores. Tenga también en cuenta que la ley aplicable puede contener restricciones y otras disposiciones relacionadas con los derechos especificados anteriormente.

## Administrador de sus datos personales e información de contacto

Responsable de privacidad, Arc'teryx, Suite 110, 2220 Dollarton Highway, North Vancouver, Columbia Británica, Canadá V7H 1A8 Correo electrónico: [privacy@arcteryx.com](mailto:privacy@arcteryx.com) Teléfono: 1-866-458-2473. 

En el caso de modificaciones o peticiones de exclusión, Arc’teryx puede retener la información personal necesaria a fines de archivo en relación con sus anteriores transacciones, además de los registros o garantías de productos.

## Preguntas o comentarios

Si tiene alguna pregunta o comentario acerca de nuestras prácticas de privacidad, póngase en contacto con el responsable de Privacidad en la dirección Arc'teryx, Suite 110, 2220 Dollarton Highway, North Vancouver, Columbia Británica, Canadá V7H 1A8, envíe un correo electrónico a [privacy@arcteryx.com](mailto:privacy@arcteryx.com) o llame por teléfono al 1-866-458-2473.

Puede llamarnos por teléfono o escribirnos a la dirección postal o de correo electrónico anteriores para solicitar una copia actualizada de nuestra política de privacidad.

Si tiene alguna pregunta sobre nuestro sitio web, escríbanos a la siguiente dirección [webmaster@arcteryx.com](mailto:webmaster@arcteryx.com) o llámenos al 1-866-458-2473 .

## Otros aspectos jurídicos

Arc’teryx se reserva el derecho a modificar esta política de privacidad en cualquier momento. Le recomendamos que la consulte periódicamente para asegurarse de que conoce y acepta los cambios de esta política de privacidad. El uso continuado de nuestro sitio web implica su consentimiento a las condiciones de esta política de privacidad y a sus actualizaciones y modificaciones.

Esta política de privacidad y todos sus gráficos, logotipos, marcas registradas y cualquier otra propiedad intelectual pertenecen a Arc’teryx y están protegidas por derechos de autor, derechos de marca y otras leyes sobre propiedad intelectual. No se permite la reproducción de nuestra propiedad intelectual sin el consentimiento expreso y por escrito de Arc’teryx.

## Gracias

Gracias por consultar esta importante información acerca de nuestra política de privacidad.

Esta política de privacidad entró en vigor el 15 de abril de 2014 y puede revisarse periódicamente.

Arc’teryx Equipment a Division of Amer Sports Canada Inc.
